Guide to the Jerome H. Holland papers, 1953-1985
Holland, Jerome H. papers, 1953-1985
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Jerome H. Holland papers, 1953-1985
2-10-2727
Jerome H. Holland, 1916-1985
49.3 cubic ft.; 2 scrapbooks
Correspondence, reports, scrapbooks, clippings, photographs, condolences, plaques.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Professional files of Jerome H. Holland, including correspondence, reports, speeches, and clippings from the various organizations with which he was involved.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Cornell University, Class of 1939. Cornell University, M.S., 1941. Ph.D. University of Pennsylvania, 1950. President of Delaware State College, Dover (1953-1960); President of Hampton Institute, Hampton, Virginia (1960-1970); Ambassador to Sweden (1970-1973). Presidential Councillor and University Trustee, Cornell University. Chairman of the American Red Cross and Planned Parenthood; board member of several corporations, director of the New York Stock Exchange, author.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, reports, scrapbooks of clippings and correspondence, photographs, and condolences. Papers pertain to the topics of Holland's presidency at Delaware St. College and Hampton Institute, membership on several corporate boards and philanthropic and social organizations including the American Red Cross and Planned Parenthood, ambassadorship to Sweden, membership on Cornell University's Board of Trustees, personal correspondence, engagment calendars, tape recordings, books, drafts of books, clippings and publicity, biographical material, speeches, plaques, and material relating to athletics.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Holland, Jerome H. (Jerome Heartwell), 1916-1985.; American Red Cross.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University. Board of Trustees.; Delaware State College.; Hampton Institute.; Planned Parenthood.
Subjects:
African Americans.; Charities.; Corporate governance.
Form and Genre Terms:
Audiotapes.; Photographs.; Scrapbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
The original folder titles used by Jerome Holland have been maintained. At the time of processing, the files were arranged alphabetically into one series.
List of plaques, medals, trophies, etc. in accession file.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Professional Files
Boxes 1-22
Series II. Writings
Boxes 22-23
Series III. Condolences
Boxes 23
Series IV.Sweden (Embassy)
Box 24-31
Series V. Photographs
Box 32-33
Series VI. Miscellaneous
Box 32, 34-48, Mapcase K AA-14, Vols. I-II
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Professional Files
  - A: General, 1942-169 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A: General, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A: General, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A: General, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A: General, 1980-1984, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A Better Chance, Inc., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adelphi University, April-July 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Advertising Council, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advertising Council, 1973-1979, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Afro-American Historical and Cultural '76 Bicentennial Corporation of Philadelphia, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Aid to Education, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aid to Education, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Aid to Education, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - AIM (Assocation for the Integration of Management, Inc.), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Akron Area Chamber of Commerce, Ohio, February- March 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alfalfa Club, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Allied Stores Corporation, September-December 1977, May 1978 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alpha Beta Boule, Sigma Pi Phi Fraternity, June 1961-January 1970, January 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Amateur Basketball Association of the United States of America, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1973-1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - American Assembly: Columbia University, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - American Assembly: Cornell University, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - American Bank and Trust Company of Pennsylvania, March-April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - American Football Coaches Association, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - American Heart Association, April-June 1964 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - American International College, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - American Management Association, 1972-1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - American Red Cross: Address for Annual Meeting of Hartford Chapter by Laura Holland, November 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - American Red Cross: Addresses to Area Chapters, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - American Red Cross: Address to Area Chapters "Challenges Confronting the Red Cross: Today and Tomorrow", 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - American Red Cross: Address to Area Chapters, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - American Red Cross: Address to Area Chapters "Areas of Concern as the Red Cross Approaches its Centennial", 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - American Red Cross: Address to Area Chapters "The American Red Cross: Its Second Century", 1981 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - American Red Cross: Address to Area Chapters "Crossroads to a New Century", 1981 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - American Red Cross: Address to Central South Carolina Chapter, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - American Red Cross: Address to Jefferson County Chapter, Watertown, NY, June 1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - American Red Cross: American Red Magen David for Israel, Annual Testimonial Luncheon to honor Jerome H. Holland, May 1984 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - American Red Cross: Appointment by President Carter as Chairman, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - American Red Cross: Appointment by President Carter as Chairman, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - American Red Cross: Biomedical Center, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - American Red Cross: Board of Governors meeting, Oct. 23, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - American Red Cross: Canadian Red Cross Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - American Red Cross: Centennial Convention, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - American Red Cross: Chairman selection, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - American Red Cross: Clippings and publicity, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Feb.-June 1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Sept.-Dec. 1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Feb.-Aug. 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Sept.-Dec. 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Feb.-May 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, June-Dec. 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Jan.-August 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Sept.-Dec. 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Jan.-March 1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, April-May 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, June-Dec. 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Jan.-Apr. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, May-Oct. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Jan.-August 1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence, Sept. 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - American Red Cross: Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - American Red Cross: Danbury, Connecticut Chapter Annual Dinner Meeting, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - American Red Cross: Data, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - American Red Cross: Data, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - American Red Cross: Data, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - American Red Cross: Data, Jan.-Aug. 1969 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - American Red Cross: Data, Sept.-Dec. 1969 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - American Red Cross: Data, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - American Red Cross: Data, 1978-1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - American Red Cross: Delaware Chapter 71st Annual Chapter Meeting, June 1976 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - American Red Cross: Dr. Charles R. Drew Sculpture donated by the Ashanti Club of Connecticut, February 24, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - American Red Cross: Executive Committee luncheon meeting, May 22, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - American Red Cross: Hawaii State Chapter Volunteer Recognition Luncheon, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - American Red Cross: History and operations, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - American Red Cross: Metropolitan Chapter Conference, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - American Red Cross: Mid-American Chapter and the United Way Meeting, June 10, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - American Red Cross: National Convention, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - American Red Cross: National Convention, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - American Red Cross: National Convention, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - American Red Cross: National Youth Services Conference, January 1980 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - American Red Cross: Northern Vermont Chapter Annual Luncheon Meeting, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - American Red Cross: Opening plenary session, May 23, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - American Red Cross: Orientation for new board members, May 21, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - American Red Cross: Photographs, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - American Red Cross: Photographs, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - American Red Cross: Presidential search, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - American Red Cross: Responses to Dr. Holland's letters on announcement of Mr. Schubert, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - American Red Cross: Speech for press conference, May 23, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - American Red Cross: Speech for St. Louis Convention by Laura Holland, May 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - American Red Cross: Strengths and weaknesses, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - American Red Cross: Virginia Capital Chapter Charter Ceremony, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - American Red Cross: Visit to European Area Headquarters Autograph Book, Sept.29-Oct. 1, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Amistad Awards, 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Amistad Research Center, 1980, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Anglo-American School, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - A.O. Smith, July-August 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Applicants, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Applicants, 1981-June 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Applicants, July 1982-Aug. 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Applicants, Sept. 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Arabian American Oil Company, August-September 1952 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Armed Force, Advisory Committee on an All-Volunteer, Jan.-May 1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Armed Force, Advisory Committee on an All-Volunteer, June 1969 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Armed Force, Advisory Committee on an All-Volunteer, Aug.-Oct. 1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Armed Force, Advisory Committee on an All-Volunteer, Nov.-Dec.2, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Armed Force, Advisory Committee on an All-Volunteer, Dec.4-6, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Armed Force, Advisory Committee on an All-Volunteer, Dec.6-20, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Armed Force, Advisory Committee on an All-Volunteer, Dec.30, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Armed Force, Advisory Committee on an All-Volunteer, Jan.2-7, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Armed Force, Advisory Committee on an All-Volunteer, Jan.9-28, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Armed Force, Advisory Committee on an All-Volunteer, Feb. 1970 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Ashville School, September 1981-August 1982 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Association of Black American Ambassadors, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Association of Black Foundation Executives, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Association of Episcopal Colleges, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Associations and clubs, Member of, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - A.T. Spaulding, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - AT & T: Audit Committee, 1979-1984 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - AT & T: Board minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - AT & T: Committee on Employee Benefits, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - AT & T: Consent decree, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - AT & T: Corporate Public Policy Committee, 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - AT & T: Corporate Public Policy Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - AT & T: Corporate Public Policy Committee: Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - AT & T: Correspondence, 1947, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - AT & T: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - AT & T: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - AT & T: Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - AT & T: Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - AT & T: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - AT & T: Directors and Officers, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - AT & T: Deferred compensation for non-employee directors, 1973-1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - AT & T: Divestiture, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - AT & T: Expense account forms, 1979, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Council, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Atrium Club, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - B: General, 1939-1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - B: General, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - B: General, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - B: General, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - B & C Associates, Inc., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bard College, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bardach, Howard, Mar.-July 1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bardach, Howard, Aug. 1978-1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Berean College, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Beth Israel Medical Center, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Biography, 1979-1985, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Bishop College, 1952, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bishop College, 1960-1964, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Black College Presidents, Council of, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Black Corporate Directors, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Black Enterprise, 1972-1980, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Black Opportunity, 1969, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Black Psychiatrists of America, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Bolden, Darwin W., 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Book material, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Boulden Academy and Seminary, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1942-1974 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Boyden International Group, Inc., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Boys' Club of America, 1939-1942, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Bradford Mutual Fund Services, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Buckner and Company, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Buttonwood Foundation, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - C: General, 1972-May 1973 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - C: General, June 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - C: General, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - C: General, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Carey, Hugh L., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Carpenter, Edmund N. III, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Carpenter, Walter S., 1960-1968 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Carter, Roland M., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Carver Community Organization: Father's Day Banquet, March-June 1961 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Central Medical Building, Inc., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Central State University, West, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Century Association, 1972-1984 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Chatham College, August-October 1979 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Audit Committee, 1979-Aug. 1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Audit Committee, Sept. 1980-Mar.ch 1981 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Audit Committee, June 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Compensation and Benefits Committee, 1981, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Correspondence, 1941-1968 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Correspondence, 1982-May 1983 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Correspondence, June 1983-1984, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Employee car lease program, 1977-1984 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Legal matters and government relations, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Public Utilization and Human Resources Committee, 1973-1984 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Retirement Funds Review Committee, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Statement of Business Philosophy and Objectives, February 17, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Chrysler Corporation: Tournament of the Roses, December 1968-January 1969 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Citizens Advisory Committee, Food and Drug Administration, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Clippings and publicity, 1938-1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Clippings and publicity, 1968-1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Clippings and publicity, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Clippings and publicity, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Clippings and publicity, 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Clippings and publicity (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Coatesville Area Chamber of Commerce, Pennsylvania, February 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Colgate University Commencement, June 1, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - College of the Virgin Islands, 1974-1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Commercial Credit Co., 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Committee of 100, Dallas Involvement, Inc., May-December 1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Compensation, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Con Edison: Westchester County Sports Program, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Conference Board, 1974-1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Conflict of Interest study, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Congratulatory commendations, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut General Life Insurance Company, 1975-1976, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Constance Culver Foundation (Westchester Clubman), 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Continental Corporation Foundation, 1973-1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Continental Corporation: New building, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Continental Insurance Companies and Continental Corporation, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Audit Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Audit Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Audit Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Correspondence, Jan.-May 1968 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Correspondence, June-Dec. 1968 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Correspondence, Jan.-Nov. 1969 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Correspondence, Dec. 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Correspondence, 1982-1984, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: MOAC, subsidiary (Marine Office-Appleton & Cox Corp.), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Public Policy Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Public Policy Committee, Jan.-June 1983 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Continental Insurance Companies: Public Policy Committee, Aug. 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Cooper, David D., 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Coors, Adolph Company, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Cornell Club, 1944-1978, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Cornell Fund, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Cornell Fund, 1978-1979, Jan.-Aug. 1979 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Cornell Fund, 1979-1980, Sept.-Dec. 1979 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Cornell Fund, 1979-1980, Jan.-May 1980 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cornell Fund, 1980-1981, June 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Cornell University: Aeronautical Laboratory, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cornell University: Alumni Clubs, 1965-1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cornell University: Athletic Hall of Fame, 1978-1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees I., 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees II., 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees III., 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees IV., 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, June 1967, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, August 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, October 1967 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, November-December 1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, January 1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, June 1968 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, July 1968 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, August 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees, April-May 1978 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Correspondence I., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Correspondence II., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Correspondence III., 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Correspondence IV., 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Correspondence V., 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Correspondence VI., 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Correspondence VII., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Correspondence VIII., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Correspondence IX., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Correspondence X., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Correspondence XI., 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Data, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Roster, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cornell University: Board of Trustees Roster, 1968-1969, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University: Class of 1939 Fund/Reunion, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Cornell University: Class of 1983 Convocation (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Cornell University: Committee on Board Memberships, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, 1937-1945 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, 1946-1957 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, 1958-June 1959 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, July 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, 1962-1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Cornell University: Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 21)